Take Submarine into the sea
We just bought this
Really very good handsome
Just tided at the river side
I just want to get in now.
Really good, very admirable.
Really powerful.
Suneo, take me to get in as well
Of course good, please
Do you want me not to sit, Suneo?
Yes, you please, too
Of course I can get in as well.
No no
Why, what does it matter
if one more with me?
We have to drive the sea shore only
three people allowed except me,
daddy and mommy
Nobita, you'd better be
a man, give it up.
Besides it can only take
five people, don't blame me.
I have to get away what mommy told me
to do and then come back,wait for me.
I have to tell mommy as well.
Hurry HP
Daddy, are you ready?
Wait a moment further.
Nobita, we are gone
No big mouth! What special about
the yacht? We take Submarine.
Every time when I get into trouble, you
save me. You are really a nice person.
Of course, we are friends.You wait here
I will bring Submarine here.
Yes, it's this.
What's that?
Submarine
That's too extreme, even
play me around at this time.
Not play you around. Wait and see.
Put it into water, it becomes big or
small according to the surroundings.
Doraemon, is this real?
Does it go under water?
Of course, come on, Nobita
Taking Submarine in bath room
does not make fun at all.
I know you want to be in the sea,right?
How to?
This submarine can move
rapidly with help of water.
Although one time move is not far
several times move will make it.
Water is everywhere anyway
Let's go. We
almost catch up Suneo and others
Go from here south
if you want to the sea
Set the direction due south first
Start up, move.
Wow, full of ice.
Is this south pole?
Wow, it's giant.
Hm, what, strange things inside.
No, help.
Hateful.
What was that, UFO?
Wow, strange fish.
It's gold fish, move further.
Wow, I feel dizzy
Hurry up moving further.
What is this color?
quite dick and familiar
How disgusting place! What is it then?
Finally stopped.
Excuse me, sorry.
Already in the sea?
Still not
But are these people in bath suits?
We can be crunched, move.
Where is it this time?
Ver strange form.
Oh, it's toilette, move fast.
Really can't take it
Every move to very strange place
Almost into the sea.
Oh, again very strange place
Next move will be into the sea
Are you sure?
I am sure, it won't be wrong.
Wow, move fast.
Into the sea.
This is sea.
Well, why so soon becomes dark?
Turn on the headlight.
Should be in the sea, correct.
It seems becoming hot.
It's true.
Very hot.
How do you feel? Handsome, right?
This is fast yacht carrying you.
Same word since a while.
It's too exiting, sol speak louder.
Thirsty? Drink a hot tea.
I said, already in the sea.
Cool it down here.
That's right.
Hi, Nobita
Let's sit down.
I would lie to ask you, Nobita
Friendship capsule
Doraemon, help yourself, please
Suneo even asks me to eat, really seldom
Eating so much
Is this a dream? Thanks.
If w.“
Really?
If you move out of Nobita's home
and become my own robot
You will have enough Dorayaki everyday.
Think about it.
You treat me like three-year-old.
I never agree with that.
Don't be angry, I am thinking for you.
But thanks a lot, you really villain.
Hateful, remember, Doraemon
I can to back to Nobita
because of Dorayaki
This is really Doraemon, wonderful.
Nobita also buys Dorayaki forme
Ten or twenty are only minor things.
Impossible
But, thank you, Doraemon
Please help me from today on.
Of course, my job is
to let Nobita have a happy life.
Let's be good friend forever.
Doraemon
Doraemon gave
Dorayaki twenty
Hm, eat them at my home at once
pretend to have done nothing.
I really can't take him, so shameless.
Doraemon, come down.
Aren't you ashamed as Nobi's family
member,but eat in others' home?
I don't care but leave you free
Why so?
It was because Suneo asked me eat it.
Return Dorayaki's cost.
I have no money.
Then let's do it this way: Lend me a
magic weapon from your pocket.
That would be traitor against Nobita.
No problem, Doraemon
As long as he does do bad things.
Actually,
I want to be a friend with a person
As long as you help me
I will forget about Dorayaki
Doraemon, then you help him.
Okay, I will lend you friendship
capsule and the controller.
Stick the capsule onto other's face,
then you take the controller.
The other will feel your friendship
and do everything for you.
Thanks
It's sad to get friend with machine.
No use to use that
I also have Doraemon this friend
I also have Nobita this friend
What's the matter?
I want to see Suneo
Little Suneo
Doraemon
Suneo
Doraemon, you come
Oh, it's friendship capsule.
But when and how did
he stick it onto Doraemon
We are good friends.
Doraemon, come on
don't go with him.
Doraemon, wait a minute.
Beat the damned guy.
If Suneo says so, the I will...
Doraemon, wait a moment
Well done.
Let's go.
Hateful villain.
Ouch, Suneo
It's Gian
Hi, what attitude do you have.
I won't show you my bud
any more from today on.
Right
I have strong partner here.
What hateful guy do you mean?
Doraemon
You are really brave.
Look at me.
Haha, you can't do anything
you want any more.
But I still have strong partners.
That's right.
That capsule must be some place
We must hurry up to take it away.
Listen, everybody. From today
on you have to follow my order.
What
Who wants to listen to you?
Nobody!
You don't agree, right?
Doraemon, teach them a lesson.
This guy can't
listen more.
Come on
Help, Doraemon
You even abuse Suneo, unforgivable.
Hm, what am I doing?
Doraemon
Oh, damaged.
Nobita
Doraemon, you have friendship
capsule sticked on, take it down.
Wait a moment, again by Suneo...
Really? Nothing under neck ring.
Nothing inside the ring bell.
Nothing in the pocket.
Where is it?
Suneo
Doraemon
Doraemon, controller is repaired
Get Nobita away.
Look at me.
Painful, very painful.
This way nobody bothers.
Go to my home.
Doraemon
It will become a prop
for the star if taken out.
A prop to become a
professional baseball player.
You are too greedy.
With this stuff you will listen
to me whatever I say.
Too bad, out of function again, hateful.
Run away.
Stop, you are my robot.
How many times you want me say?
lam not at all.
Be careful.
Doraemon, come up.
Come up
In fact friendship capsule sticks here.
There will be nothing.
Controller is okay again.
Doraemon, come back
Suneo
How come?
I will never leave you, Suneo.
Help
Goku cross
Too bad, overslept.
Why does mommy not wake me up?
You don't get up
however I wake you.
No time, finished, late.
Too late, even no homework
done. You will be punished.
I am criticized again. All is
your false not wake me up.
You will become angry
if wake you up.
Later on not ask mommy any more
You too, forced me writing homework
then I won't be criticized.
What are you talking about. All is your
false. You even dare to say others.
When I ask you write homework
which time you listened to me?
Doraemon, can you let others
lend me the non-lazy prop?
I can lend you that Goku ring.
Put this on your head and it will grasp
or loose your head if say close or open
Because it can hurt, I can't be lazy.
Very good, lend it to me.
But you are not brave person
will give up soon.
You still don't believe me. Really want
to get rid of this lazy habit?
Well, sorry but I will lend it to you.
Really?
L' may ma.
No, you can leave
after finishing the homework.
Wait a moment, anyway the same.
Close
It hurts, very painful, not like that.
It won't stop if you can read.
No, I feel dizzy if suddenly
let me write so much.
Let the brain have a rest.
Close
painful, very painful, painful
You can't take off that head ring
if nobody helps you do so.
Doraemon is devil, devil.
Finally finished it.
Almost tired, it seems that
you wrote it for ten years.
Nobita, This is very urgent
Help me send it, fast.
No, I am too tired.
I go, I go there.
If I know it, I will ask him to do so.
Oh, yes, then ask Shizuka do so.
What, Nobita
Beautiful hair band
NO so, Shizuka will get
headache if put this on.
Why?
Close it
very painful
So it is.
How pitiful.
NO, for his good, don't take it away.
Really?
That's too much extreme, Shizuka
you saw me painful face.
It seemed very painful.
But real friends want to help
him get rid of the habit.
That's true,
I won't help you take it off.
Shizuka, wait a moment, wait, Shizuka
What are you talking about, fellow?
Close it tightly.
Very painful.
I am helping my mommy shopping
you help me buy it.
Why should I help you buy it?
This way, close.
I go, I will go there.
You are very noisy, I just borrowed it.
Wow, really funny.
Who, who makes my grandson crying?
I was just surprised
but just wanted to borrow it.
In fact it's Nobita.
What's that, very handsome head ring.
Nobita, what are you wearing?
Can you lend me that?
No.
Why? Can't take it.
Finally take it down.
Haha, very handsome, really handsome.
I am back.
Gian, close the door after getting in.
Painful very painful,
what's the matter actually?
It's steamed bred.
Eating it off is painful, very painful.
Hi, Nobita, you even ask me
put on this strange stuff.
Nipping you is very painful
(Nipping sound the same like closing)
Help me, mommy.
Oh, head ring disappears.
This return to you,
you deal with your own matter.
Bye
Close it, close it
Very painful
I also want that head ring
then you have to work hard
Although no more Goku head ring,
he understands self open and close.
Really wonderful
It is quite comfortable if done
according to one's own way.
Nobita
Oh,it's Shizuka, I go down now.
Nobita, you just decided
working hard, right?
Wait a moment, I am going.
I don't care about you any more.
Apartment tree
Be careful
Come on
Nobita, change hand
I know
change hand
Change hand
Watch out my sword
very painful
How is it?
One, two, go on.
Can you please be quite?
If you want to play, go out playing.
You want to be back?
Play next time
Let's go.
Bye
Nobita, what's the matter with you?
Make the room so chaotic.
Bring it in order.
I don't want to do meaningless things.
It will be chaotic again
Don't bring it in order, then.
What do you say?
I don't allow you do so.
I know, I clean it at once.
Doraemon also help cleaning
You can lie prone and eat stuffs.
Really
We go out.
No sound when walking.
Where do you two go? Wait a moment
This is for Govt».
Who is Gore'?
He is my cousin.
Admitted by college, therefore come back
from countryside into his own apartment
Seemingly very tasteful
This is made by ante for
my Mochi. Thanks a lot.
Very chaotic place although
it has nothing to do with me.
A group of friends came here
last night playing until this morning.
I feel very sleepy.
I am also hungry.
You even lie prone when eating.
No more lessons.
Really very free
Nobody can it.
Well, we also rent an
apartment and move out.
What? Don't bother anybody.
That's right, you are still a pupil.
I am already determined.
Joking has also border.
No more nonsense, go and read.
Heavily criticized.
Of course.
But, I can't give up this idea.
Hm, then use that for having a look.
What is that?
Although it's a toy in 22nd century.
Apartment tree
First time using this
read the manual first.
Then plant the little trees
they become big three minutes later
at once if poring with water.
Then it turns to be an apartment.
Really amazing.
Three minutes later.
Is this the apartment?
As if it were true.
Landing
Doraemon
Hurry up down, come on
Wow, really great.
Still below
In the manual it says the
roots will turn to rooms
Really great, wonderful
Move and live here immediately.
What, moving?
Hm, I found free apartment.
Wait a moment, Nobita
He is kidding. How
come with free apartment?
Cannot set it into.
It does not matter,
put it into my pocket first.
It will be okay
after getting into the room.
Apartment
Rent is 100 $ a month.
I take it
Help me carry this.
I know now
I also bring TV set
All luggage fit in.
Wonderful
Really wonderful
Start the adventure.
Room are plenty.
You choose on your own.
This room is bigger. We
use it as playing room
No problem to play over night.
Dance, sing
Where were you for dinner?
I hear sound coming from here.
Nobita, dinner time.
It's mommy.
I already move to here.
I will be angry if nonsense further.
It's better going home in the evening.
Don't make parents angry.
I am also hungry.
See you tomorrow.
Bye, bye.
Doraemon, hurry
to the apartment.
What's the matter?
Buried
It says apartment tree will be
bad and buried in the earth.
Apartment disappears
Excuse me, excuse me.
Dig my TV set and sofa out.
My piano as well
Where are my stuffs?
asia_cartoons@sinaman.com
Use Time machine to get the inmates
Today is really a good day. Until school
off day no teacher criticizes us.
Really rare good thing
mommy should praise us
We want cake and coffee.
So decided.
Who is here?
Hi, hurry up and get away.
Wow, just like my sound.
Painful, very painful
Over there in my classroom
What is it, very strange.
What's the matter?
Hi, you did that, Nobita
What was the sound?
Hi, who was that? Who did that?
He broke it. It was Nobita.
No, it wasn't me.
But there was only you
alone in this classroom.
No, Suneo, it wasn't me.
It was not me. When I came here
the glass was already broken.
Nobita, practical jokes are not good
but lie is even not forgivable.
That's right.
At the end everyday would be criticized.
Who was that?
I am looking for this.
You are indeed inmates.
Nonsense. That's not me.
It's you for sure.
It's you, correct.
If it's not me, then it's you for sure.
I did not make any mistakes.
It's hateful, you can argue against him.
You wait here.
I will find out evidence
Suneo, you wake up.
I will call Doraemon for helping me.
What, for unjustified reason
criticized by the teacher.
I will give that bad
teacher a lesson.
Wait a moment. I think the
suspect should be Suneo
Well, I will blow him in the air Suneo.
Listen to me finish first.
I wan to find the evidence.
Then you need time machine.
Well, take time machine
there and break it
Here we are
It's so quiet.
The class is not over yet.
Hi, I am sleepy now.
Hi, wake up.
You can't run out
of the classroom during class.
Principal, I did not drop the class.
Yes, yes.
You see. I am in the classroom.
That's good. That's good.
Too bad
ls the class still not over?
Only I have not
come out of the classroom.
What are you doing?
We can go home.
What are you going to play at home?
Planning slowly.
This slow mode
make you trouble.
I remember somebody
hide behind that straw hill
Why didn't you say that before?
Hiding for watching what?
Hi, somebody is coming.
Too bad, can be found by inmates.
Hi, get away from here fast.
Wow, where do you fly to?
You made me hit it that far
Pick it up and bring back.
How come?
Very painful.
Very strange.
Gian is really not okay
hit the ball so far away.
Finally it I broke it.
It seems so.
That thing during day was really strange
He even said to find evidence.
Really broken by my ball?
Of course yes.
Regardless what Nobita can do
It will be bad if Doraemon is angry.
That's right. You'd better go to
Nobita's home and apologize.
Really?
It's true. That's passed matter.
Forget it.
This means
Nobita is really good.
Shooting championship
This is Ruma 1908 automatic pistol
This is Washal TPK
This is a pistol made by Panteley
This is the pistol used by
American famous constable.
Peng, peng, really great
Hi, what is Nobita's toy gun?
You are an adult
why still play toy gun?
He has no toy gun, hahaha
That's not true,
of course I have toy gun.
Yes
Very great, one shot one hit
For such a boring thing
you can even be so good.
Your way a praising make one angry.
Maybe you think a total idiot.
If I were born one hundred years ago, I
may become a famous historical shooter.
In modern time there is no chance for me
to demonstrate my ability, really pity.
Then I help you creating chance.
What, what?
Air pistol
You treat me as an idiot.
I put this liquid on hand
say “peng“ when it's dry.
It can shoot high speed air
like jet plane to beat the enemy.
It can make the enemy
unconscious but not hurt.
What are you kidding?
Don't touch me.
You even say this to me.
You see the leaves on the trees.
Each finger has one
all together ten air pistols
Air pistol?
I want to use this pistol
for shooting games.
Everyone gets ten bullets turn around
and then face to face, start shooting.
Those who shot down are lost
That who lives the last
is the shooting master.
Good, good, funny.
I like this kind of game the most.It has
been my dream since childhood.
It seems really like cowboy in the west.
Gun out
You shoot first.
Although a few bullets,
but each shot hit.
Wow, Nobita I strong
Hi, we two unite.
You are very good in shooting.
Who says we are very bad?
Too arrogant.
Get rid of Nobita first.
Come on
Only Gian left. If I hit him down
I will be the shooting master.
There are three bullets left
here is one, there is another one.
You already used out your bullets.
I still have ten bullets because
I hid at the beginning never used them.
You are very dirty.
NO PROVE nonsense.
Clever people can get the final victory.
Where to you want me aim at?
At your head
Or your chest?
Where best?
You will get it.
Painful,
rarely to get so handsome picture.
Damned.
How are you?
Everybody looks at me surprised.
You can tell anybody you fell.
Really wonderful
You feel proud for
so long and now very hungry.
Dinner
It turns to this result
only because you said dinner.
Is any bullet left?
How come?
You shoot on over there.
Regardless what you have don
when will your mommy wake up?
Very strange, one, two, three, four
one shot for Gian.
Finebox
Taken away
Very painful
Once again.
Look at my beautiful shooting
This time look at mine.
My ball
Broken
It does not work.
What do you want, Suneo?
See how great I am shooting.
How do you compensate?
Bring another ball, hurry.
My ball was kicked broken by Gian.
Mine too.
My ball was broken yesterday by Gian.
Sometimes you bring the ball on your own
I Have a good idea.
How about everybody spends
some money buy a new ball?
Everybody spends some.
So it's relative fair.
Agree
But I still have nothing now.
I will bring it tomorrow.
Next time.
Then me, too.
You all don't want to pay anything.
Why don't you spend anything first?
Stop P
Wait a moment
Help, Doraemon
Wait a moment, I know the situation.
The you use this.
What's that?
Finebox
You will be punished as soon as you do
anything wrong
and this finebox will follow you.
Each time 100$ fine
You can save money without any efforts.
Well, then use this.
Agree
agree
Me too agree, very painful
I asked you take care of the baby
but you run out for fun each time.
Really no means against you.
Stop, I have no money.
That's my private saving.
After aiming at the goal
there is no way to get away.
Go home
me too
Why follow me?
Because you are my shelter.
Only be careful, don't be caught.
Nobita
Do your reading
I know now, I will do so.
Almost got me to criticize
The room is even like this
Bring it in order if it's so chaotic.
Really bothering.
Any time concerned to be fined.
Why have you been lazy all
the time?You deserve that.
Now Nobita must be fined.
What are you doing?
It seems that somebody is accused.
You have to know the limit
Why are you lazy all the time?
You stop, give me that 100$.
Return me that 100$. stop.
Just like an idiot.
You guy, return me that.
I caught it.
Oh, painful, okay, okay, I give up.
I said okay, don't follow me any more.
Get away.
What are you doing indeed?
Never look ahead when walking.
You come again.
What?
Hi, Gian
Suneo, help me
Help me keep the purse.
Okay
Wonderful
If I don't take money
I can't be fined even if accused.
Go home
Gian, you abuse my kid again.
I my home the same
you say what to do?
So is our dog.
Really? That's too extreme.
Sorry
Oh, I can breath now.
Really can't take it
Well, where is the finebox?
Wow, my saving box.
Stop. Don't run away.
Return to you. That's too extreme.
Gian is even in such a panic.
Really very great
Wait, you can ask me to whatever you
want, but return me the money.
Nobita's adventure.
Mommy, give me that
chopsticks if you don't want them.
Why do you need chopsticks
Okay, but don't forget learning.
Okay
So you can go out now.
That's it? Not enough.
Well, what are you doing?
Doraemon, actually I want to take bamboo
boat for a adventure to no man's island
With bamboo boat for no man's land?
With these bamboo chopsticks?
Yes, I just want to train.
(Robinson's Adventure)
In fact
it's because of having read this book.
Going to adventure is also a good thing
Okay, I lend you the gum bamboo boat.
No need
I want to rely on my own,
not on other's help.
Although this idea is very great
You need several decades
making bamboo boat with chopsticks
Okay, then I just borrow
the air bamboo boat.
No more bag on back. I build
up my life with own hands.
Okay
I won't take anybody's help.
I am going.
That bamboo dragonfly is mine.
Wonderful
Almost at the shore
come and have a look
Can't find no man's island in any way.
Do I have to stay on the sea forever? I
would have not play it if known before.
It's really true.
Still 30 minutes, otherwise...
That's it.
What to do?
Really can do anything with you.
This is the detector for no man's land.
It will marsh to
no man's island if installed.
So it's good.
Hi, bamboo boat is moving,
it's no man's land.
Wonderful, it's really Nobita.
Here we are.
It's really no man's island.
We are great.
I am the first one
discovering this island.
Well, just name it Nobita island.
For living further
we have to eat something.
In Robinson's adventure
he looked for fruit for stopping hunger
I can take it any more.
I am dying for hunger.
That's why I asked you bring bags.
If we return him this?
I would not have come
if known that before.
Am I dreaming? Very sweet.
It's fruit.
Wonderful
Still a bit less.
Very like bred taste
Is this the legendary bred tree?
It's raining. Umbrella.
Oh god.
Umbrella,
who can bring the umbrella here?
Occasionally you have to bring up
your own idea. Just make a hut.
It's a hole, just live here.
We are all wet, no cloths available,
what to do?
Right
Put the two sides together
to make a cloth
In fact these are very useful leaves.
No water we will die.
Really troublesome Robinson
It's a spring.
It's almost dark.
No electricity, no TV
no bed, we want home.
Mommy
Doraemon, Nobita.
Come on.
Doraemon, where is Nobita?
Over there.
Why not go home?
Painful
What are you doing? It's so late.
Why not go home?
Mommy
I will never forgive you
Do you hear that? Nobita
mommy
Living in mountain hole,
drinking spring water. So we stay alive
Nobita is really a reliable person.
Somebody's face is round
Somebody's face is long
Somebody's face is square
Somebody's face is triangle
If cry. become angry
play temper
Crying one will become a devil.
But be happy and laugh.
Everybody's face is actually round.